(city_data = [
  {
    "question": "What is the population of Washington, DC as of 2019?",
    "option_1": "1) 633,427",
    "option_2": "2) 711,571",
    "option_3": "3) 800, 331",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How many senators does Washington, DC.have?",
    "option_1": "1) One",
    "option_2": "2) Two",
    "option_3": "3) Zero",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What two states border Washington, DC?",
    "option_1": "1) VA & DE",
    "option_2": "2) MD & WV",
    "option_3": "3) VA & MD",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the street address of the White House?",
    "option_1": "1) 1600 Pennsylvania Ave.",
    "option_2": "2) 123 Capital St.",
    "option_3": "3) 1000 North Capital St.",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "In which war were the Capital, Treasure, and White House burned down?",
    "option_1": "1) Civil War",
    "option_2": "2) War of 1812",
    "option_3": "3) World War I",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which educational foundation maintains most museums in DC and keeps them free?",
    "option_1": "1) Peabody",
    "option_2": "2) Macarthur",
    "option_3": "3) Smithsonian",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "The ______ Center for Performing Arts is named after which former President?",
    "option_1": "1) Kennedy",
    "option_2": "2) Adams",
    "option_3": "3) Eisenhower",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which university in Washington shares a name with the neighborhood in which it is located?",
    "option_1": "1) Howard University",
    "option_2": "2) Gallaudet University",
    "option_3": "3) Georgetown University",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "The National ___ houses many of DC's museums and institutions.",
    "option_1": "1) Park",
    "option_2": "2) Mall",
    "option_3": "3) Monument",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How tall is the Washington Monument?",
    "option_1": "1) 800 ft.",
    "option_2": "2) 555 ft.",
    "option_3": "3) 586 ft.",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first president to live in the White House?",
    "option_1": "1) John Adams",
    "option_2": "2) George Washington",
    "option_3": "3) John F. Kennedy",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The streets in D.C. that run diagonally are named after ____.",
    "option_1": "1) Numbers",
    "option_2": "2) Words",
    "option_3": "3) States",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which genre of music (combining hip-hop and live band music) originated in DC?",
    "option_1": "1) Slam Poetry",
    "option_2": "2) Go-Go",
    "option_3": "3) Emo",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which \"letter\" street is missing in Washington, DC?",
    "option_1": "1) K",
    "option_2": "2) M",
    "option_3": "3) J",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which famous sci-fi movie character is featured as a gargoyle on the National Cathedral?",
    "option_1": "1) Capt. Picard",
    "option_2": "2) Darth Vader",
    "option_3": "3) Frodo Baggins",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What institution in the DC area has 17 miles of corridors?",
    "option_1": "1) Capital Building",
    "option_2": "2) National Archives",
    "option_3": "3) Pentagon",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What DC institution houses the United States Constitution & Declaration of Independence?",
    "option_1": "1) National Archives",
    "option_2": "2) Library of Congress",
    "option_3": "1) White House",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How many bathrooms are in the White House?",
    "option_1": "1) 35",
    "option_2": "2) 10",
    "option_3": "3) 55",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The Reflecting Pool sits between the Washington Monument and The ____.",
    "option_1": "1) White House",
    "option_2": "2) Vietnam Memorial",
    "option_3": "3) Lincoln Memorial",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which neighborhood, dating back to 1751, is the oldest part of the city?",
    "option_1": "1) Adams Morgan",
    "option_2": "2) Georgetown",
    "option_3": "3) Foggy Bottom",
    "answer": 2
  }
])
